<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Indore Visita</string>

    <!--Strings used for onNavigationItemSelected-->
    <string name="title_landmarks">City Landmarks</string>
    <string name="title_eatery">City Eateries</string>
    <string name="title_shopping">City Shopping Centres</string>
    <string name="title_excursions">Excursions</string>
    <string name="title_about_city">About City</string>
    <string name="title_city_history">City History</string>
    <string name="title_city_culture">City Culture</string>
    <string name="title_how_to_reach">How to reach</string>


    <!--Strings used for onNavigationItemSelected-->

    <string name="about_city">The beautiful city of Indore in Madhya Pradesh state of <b>India</b>
        is located on the banks of the River Khan and Sarawati and is known for its architectural
        splendor in the form of monuments, palaces, and forts.
        \nIndore is a home to many industries, like automobile, textile, IT, and it gives ample
        of scopes to students and businessmens to find work opportunities in the city. The city
        have emerged as commercial capital and IT hub of Madhya Pradesh. The most famous institutes
        and companies are IIM Indore, DAVV, TCS, Infosys, Yash Technology.
        IIT Indore and Crystal IT Park are part of the great educational and
        technology center of Indore.
        \nThe city is famous for its food, festival, and handicrafts that give tourists a wide
        opportunity to spend quality time with family and friends and relish their holidays in the
        heart of India i.e. Madhya Pradesh.</string>

    <string name="city_history">The history of Indore is a tale of strife between the Mughals,
        Marathas and the British who were struggling to gain dominance of central India.
        According to the records, it was one Rao Nandlal Chaudhary who founded the city of Indore.
        When the Marathas came into power, they lost the third Battle of Panipath to Ahmad Shah
        Abdali, an Afghan invader. After that, they became powerless to resist the British and had
        to sue for peace. Under these terms, the Holkars became the rulers of Indore.
        \nMaharaja Malhar Rao Holkar was the founder of the Holkar dynasty. He was one of the
        greatest statesmen an warrior of his times. Indore remained as a part of the Holkar
        princedom during the British Raj. During the independence of India, it joined with a
        number of neighbouring princely states and became a part of Madhya Bharat. The latter
        was merged into Madhya Pradesh on November 1, 1956. </string>

    <string name="city_culture">The cultural heritage of Indore includes magnificent remains of its
        glorious past, soulful religious places and beautiful surroundings. Indore culture is a
        unique blend of various cultures from across the country and makes it a perfect destination
        to be explored. You will be enthralled to see the royalty and the simplicity of the city.
        It is known for its food and festivals and welcomes the visitors with warmth.\n Indore
        presents a good example of unity in diversity with major population of Hindus, sizeable
        minorities of Muslims, Janis, Christians and sikhs and Buddhists.There are a number
        of migrants in the city from different parts of nation too.
        \n The city has a true cosmopolitan nature. You will find people belonging to different
        cultural backgrounds and speaking varied languages. The major languages spoken in Indore
        are Hindi, Marathi, English, Rajasthani, Malwi, Punjabi and Sindhi.</string>

    <string name="how_to_reach"><b>By Air:</b> Indore is conveniently located in the center of
        India, making it easily accessible from all the major cities like Bhopal, Gwalior,
        Ahmedabad, Hyderabad, Kolkata, Nagpur, Jaipur, Raipur, Delhi and Mumbai. Indore airport is
        just 8 km away from the city and one can hire a prepaid taxi or even take a bus from the
        airport to reach hotel.
        \n<b>By Rail:</b> Indore railway station is connected through Ratlam division of the
        western railway and is accessible from the major citities in India including Mumbai, Pune,
        Nagpur, Delhi, Jaipur, Ahmedabad, and Vadodra.
        \n<b>By Road:</b> Indore is well connected to other cities of the state through state and
        national highways. Regular bus service is available from cities like Bhopal, Gwalior,
        Ujjain, and Sanchi to reach Indore</string>

    <!--Strings used for venue details-->

    <!--Strings used for landmarks details-->

    <string name="landmark1_title">Rajawada</string>
    <string name="landmark1_description">Synonymous with the heart of Indore city, it stands
        today as a mute witness to the bygone splendour of the Holkar rulers. This 200 year old
        seven-story historic palace of the Holkars is built in a mixture of Muslim, Maratha
        and French styles. The lower three floors are made of stone and the upper floors are
        made of wood, which made it very vulnerable to destruction by fire. Rajwada was burnt
        three times in its history; the last fire in 1984 took the greatest toll.Today only the
        front facade remains. Recent renovations have recreated some of the old glory of this
        beautiful palace.</string>
    <string name="landmark1_location">Rajwada circle</string>
    <string name="landmark1_fee">Indian Citizens – ₹ 10
        \nForeign nationals – ₹ 250
        \nVideography – ₹ 100
        \nPhotography – ₹ 25</string>
    <string name="landmark1_timing">10:00 am to 5:00 pm; closed on Mondays </string>
    <string name="landmark1_maps">https://goo.gl/maps/kfjLuCqgjAr</string>

    <string name="landmark2_title">Lal Baag Palace</string>
    <string name="landmark2_description">One of the grandest monuments the Holkar dynasty left
        Indore. A reflection of their taste, grandeur and lifestyle, its construction began in 1886
        under Tukoji Rao Holkar II, and was carried out in three phases. The final phase was
        completed in 1921 under Tukoji Rao Holkar III. Many royal receptions were held here.
        It has a total area of 28 hectares, and at one time it had the reputation of having one
        of the best rose gardens in the country.</string>
    <string name="landmark2_location">Indira Nagar</string>
    <string name="landmark2_fee">₹ 10</string>
    <string name="landmark2_timing">10:00 am to 5:00 pm; closed on Mondays </string>
    <string name="landmark2_maps">https://goo.gl/maps/xUwbG7um8SU2</string>

    <string name="landmark3_title">Bada Ganpati</string>
    <string name="landmark3_description"> This Hindu Temple was built in the year 1875. According
        to the mythology, one of the residents of the city of Avantika or Ujjain dreamt of Lord
        Ganesh in his sleep. So, he rose up on the next day and prepared for the enormous statue
        of Lord Ganesha, so that the Lord blesses him.
        Better known for its size than antiquity, this temple
        houses perhaps the largest Ganesh idol in the world measuring 25 feet from crown to foot.
        Created as a result of the dream of an Avantika (Ujjain) resident, Shri Dadhich,
        it was built in 1875.</string>
    <string name="landmark3_location">Malhar Gunj</string>
    <string name="landmark3_timing">5:00 am to 12:00 pm and 4:00 pm to 8:00 pm, Daily</string>
    <string name="landmark3_maps">https://goo.gl/maps/BLiYv9pS3tj</string>

    <string name="landmark4_title">Kanch Mandir</string>
    <string name="landmark4_description">This Jain temple is an architectural marvel in glass.
        The walls, ceilings, floors, pillars and door knobs are entirely inlaid with glass.
        Even paintings are done in glass. Atop is a special glass chamber which multiplies the
        three statues of Lord Shantinath, Aadinath &amp; Mahavira installed there into an indefinite
        number (said to be visible up to 24 times, corresponding to the 24 tirthankaras).</string>
    <string name="landmark4_location">Hukumchand Marg, Itwaria Bazaar</string>
    <string name="landmark4_timing">5:00 am to 12:00 pm and 4:00 pm to 8:00 pm , Daily</string>
    <string name="landmark4_maps">https://goo.gl/maps/DwjZM5Jsf1M2</string>

    <string name="landmark5_title">Gandhi Hall</string>
    <string name="landmark5_description">Built in 1904 and originally named King Edwards Hall,
        it was renamed Mahatma Gandhi Hall in 1948. Its architectural style is Indo-Gothic.
        Made in Seoni stone, its domes and staples are a landmark of Indore today. It has a
        four-faced clock tower in front, because of which it is locally known as Ghanta Ghar.
        It is frequently the venue for the various book and painting exhibitions, fairs and
        festivals held throughout the year. The building also has a library, a children\'s park
        and a temple.</string>
    <string name="landmark5_location">Indore GPO</string>
    <string name="landmark5_timing">10 AM to 6 PM, Daily</string>
    <string name="landmark5_maps">https://goo.gl/maps/gqkCkXN7gNT2</string>

    <string name="landmark6_title">Annapurna Mandir</string>
    <string name="landmark6_description">Prominent temple dedicated to the Hindu goddess of food
        featuring an ornate gate &amp; elephant statues. </string>
    <string name="landmark6_location">Kranti Kriplani Nagar</string>
    <string name="landmark6_maps">https://goo.gl/maps/XxxXQ8VXB7K2</string>
    <string name="landmark6_timings">07:00 AM to 08:00 PM, Daily</string>

    <string name="landmark7_title">Krishnapura Chhatri</string>
    <string name="landmark7_description">Krishnapura Chhatri are the tombs or cenotaphs erected in memory of
        dead Holkar rulers and their family members. The Chhatris picturesquely poised on the Khan
        river banks near Rajawada are incomparable in terms of Maratha architecture and sculpture
        of their period. At Chhatri Baag is the main collection of tombs housed in two compounds.
        Close by is the beautiful Bolia Sarkar's Chhatri constructed in 1858 AD in memory of Sardar
        Chimnaji Appa Sahib Bolia.</string>
    <string name="landmark7_location">Mahatma Gandhi Road</string>
    <string name="landmark7_maps">https://goo.gl/maps/stgzapPqFio</string>
    <string name="landmark7_timings">09:00 AM to 05:00 PM; closed on Sundays</string>

    <string name="landmark8_title">Khajrana Ganesh Temple</string>
    <string name="landmark8_description">Khajrana Ganesh Temple is a pilgrimage center in Indore,
        dedicated to Lord Ganpanti. This Temple is built in 1735 by Rani Ahilya Bai Holkar.
        The devotees circling around temple and tie a thread to pray Lord Ganesha for successfully
        completion of his work. The idol was found in a well and in 1735, it was taken out from
        the well and a temple was established in 1735 by Ahilyabai Holkar belonging to the Holkar
        dynasty of the Maratha Empire. It is said that the ancient statue in the temple statue was
        seen in a dream of a local Pandit Mangal Bhatt. After this dream, the queen Ahilya Bai
        Holkar excavated and installed the idol from under the ground and installed it. From where
        the statue was removed, there is a well, which is right in front of the temple.</string>
    <string name="landmark8_location">Khajrana Rd, Ganeshpuri Colony</string>
    <string name="landmark8_maps">https://goo.gl/maps/rkXnSmy4zyQ2</string>
    <string name="landmark8_timings">5 AM to 8 PM</string>
    <string name="landmark8_website">http://www.shreeganeshkhajrana.com/</string>

    <string name="landmark9_title">Gomatgiri</string>
    <string name="landmark9_description"> On the hill 10-12 km away from the heart of the city,
        the Jain Samaj has constructed a 21 feet statue of Lord Gomateshwar, a replica of the
        Bahubali statue of Shravanbelagola. Also built here are 24 marble temples with shilars
        for each tirthankar. This place offers a breathtaking view of Indore city by night. </string>
    <string name="landmark9_location">Nainod Village, Indore</string>
    <string name="landmark9_maps">https://goo.gl/maps/RhCKVFC6wro</string>
    <string name="landmark9_timings">6:00 AM to 12:00 PM and  2:00 PM to 7:00 PM</string>


    <!--String resources for excursions-->

    <string name="excursion1_title">Nakhrali Dhani Water Park</string>
    <string name="excursion1_description">Nakhrali Dhani blends Rajasthani and Malwi culture and
        presents before the visitors a never-ending charm and magnificence to imbibe them into
        the celebration. It inculcates- traditional dance performances by
        Rajasthani dancers, entertaining Puppet shows, Bullock Cart Rides, Camel ride, magic show,
        Horse ride and indeed a sumptuous Rajasthani meal. The village resort also
        includes- a clean and hygienic swimming pool, a dance zone and a separate dining hall with
        low rise sittings and a affectionately served food.The mouth-watering cuisines served in
        the large dining hall are a treat of lifetime. .</string>
    <string name="excursion1_location">Rau</string>
    <string name="excursion1_maps">https://goo.gl/maps/pf8iGaqo4LT2</string>
    <string name="excursion1_timing">11 AM to 11 PM</string>
    <string name="excursion1_fee">Children with ht les than 3 ft - free
    \nChildren with ht from 3 ft to 4 ft 3 in - ₹ 330
    \nAdults - ₹ 490
    \nWater Park charges - ₹ 110</string>
    <string name="excursion1_website">http://www.nakhralidhani.com/</string>

    <string name="excursion2_title">Regional Park</string>
    <string name="excursion2_description">If you are the kind of a person who does not want to do
        much then the regional park along the banks of Pipliapala Lake is going to be your thing.
        There are beautiful gardens, Mughal Garden, French Garden in the premises of Pipliyapala
        Regional Park Indore which add to the beauty of the already mesmerizing place. There is
        also an open amphi theatre which is a site for many theatrical activities for the pleasure
        of the visitors here. The beautiful lake at Pipliyapala Regional Park is fitted with
        a couple of jet fountains and lights which make it a sight not to be missed in the night.
        A perfect spot for a little picnic for that ultimate Kodak Moment. There are plans of
        getting boating facility, a children park and a food court to the table for a wholesome
        experience for the visitors in the near future.</string>
    <string name="excursion2_location">Rajiv Gandhi Circle</string>
    <string name="excursion2_maps">https://goo.gl/maps/aHgwcwt7V6S2</string>
    <string name="excursion2_fee">Adults - ₹ 25
    \nChildren - ₹ 10</string>
    <string name="excursion2_timings">8 AM to 10 PM</string>

    <string name="excursion3_title">Tincha Waterfalls</string>
    <string name="excursion3_description">Tincha Falls, is an ideal weekend getaway. The water
        drips from a height of about 300 ft and it facilitates for bathing in the river upstream.
        The exhuberent and spectacular waterfall has a pond nearby, which enhances the beauty of
        the place. Its a sight to behold especially in the monsoons when it is in full and furious
        flow. From a distance, the waterfall appears like streams of milk rushing down the
        mountainside.There is also a couple of pools because of the cascading water everywhere
        that you can swim in, making Tincha Falls a great place for a day full of fun and
        frolic.</string>
    <string name="excursion3_location">Berchha Village, 24km from Indore</string>
    <string name="excursion3_maps">https://goo.gl/maps/PJ4gAVQhkaB2</string>

    <string name="excursion4_title">Choral Dam</string>
    <string name="excursion4_description">Choral Dam and the lake formed in front is another great
        place to visit on a short trip. For those looking to get away from the busy city life and
        enjoy nature in close quarters, this is the place to be. Great views and a beautiful
        waterfall here will definitely leave you feeling refreshed. If you are looking for some
        activity during your visit, you can also choose to go on a boat ride; speed and paddle
        boats are available for hire.</string>
    <string name="excursion4_location">Rampuria, 24 km from Indore</string>
    <string name="excursion4_maps">https://goo.gl/maps/w2phv7R58zm</string>

    <string name="excursion5_title">Crescent Water Park</string>
    <string name="excursion5_description">Water is filled with thrilling rides and water
        sports. Enjoy a fun filled day with your family and friends at this place with its water
        park,amusement park and restaurant.</string>
    <string name="excursion5_location">Near Devguradia, Khurd Kapmle Road, Indore</string>
    <string name="excursion5_maps">https://goo.gl/maps/DKKKFKMbH7k</string>
    <string name="excursion5_timings">10:00 AM to 06:00 PM</string>
    <string name="excursion5_website">http://www.crescentwaterpark.in/</string>

    <string name="excursion6_title">Patalpani Waterfalls</string>
    <string name="excursion6_description">The Patalpani Waterfall is located in Mhow Tehsil of
        Indore district in the state of Madhya Pradesh, India. The waterfall is
        approximately 300 feet high. The area around Patalpani is a popular picnic and trekking
        spot. The water flow is highest immediately after the rainy season (usually after July).
        It goes almost dry in the summer season, and the stream is reduced to a trickle.</string>
    <string name="excursion6_location">Kekariya Dabri, 33 km from Indore</string>
    <string name="excursion6_maps">https://goo.gl/maps/BjvAc6SxiTA2</string>


    <!--String resources for eateries-->

    <string name="eatery1_title">Sarafa</string>
    <string name="eatery1_description">No one knows about the exact origins of this bazar, and if
        stories are to be believed, jewelry store owners in the locality encouraged the bazaar
        by giving stall owners space in front of their shops so as to secure their shops at night.
        What an innovative idea, right?
        \nIt is a jewelry market during daytime, but when darkness falls, the place turns into a
        food street with a mouth-watering range of items. This marketplace has a lot to offer
        in terms of food as well as nightlife, making Sarafa Bazar extremely popular among locals
        as well as tourists. This is one of the greatest places to visit in Indore with friends,
        and you all can try out some very interesting items like Poha, Jalebis, Khichadi,
        Malpua…the list goes on and on! Another factor making this place a must-visit is that it is
        hardly a kilometer away from the city center.</string>
    <string name="eatery1_location">Bada Sarafa Market</string>
    <string name="eatery1_maps">https://goo.gl/maps/Rn1mqYcsBEr</string>
    <string name="eatery1_fee">Bhutte Ka Kees, Ratalu, Rabri, Kulfi, Khopra Patties, Jalebi,
        Garadu, and Poha-Jalebi (also known as Indori Poha)</string>
    <string name="eatery1_timings">After 8:00 PM to 4:00 AM</string>

    <string name="eatery2_title">Chappan Dukaan</string>
    <string name="eatery2_description">Are you a foodie? Do you like to try out new dishes?
        Does the very thought of delicious treats makes your mouth water? Then Chappan Dukan,
        which is located around 4.5 km from the city center, is the perfect place to go to
        when you are in Indore. Chappan Dukan is a Hindi name, which translates into ’56 shops’.
        True to its name, this was once a place with 56 individual shops. However, today you can
        find here a wide variety of food stalls, all buzzing with diners. The atmosphere here is
        lively and it is among the perfect places to visit in Indore at night. Imagine taking food
        trip through a street full of eateries, each offering something delicious to tickle your
        taste buds. </string>
    <string name="eatery2_location">56 Dukan St, New Palasia</string>
    <string name="eatery2_maps">https://goo.gl/maps/PYLouns6mZP2</string>
    <string name="eatery2_fee">Khopra Patties, Paani Puri, Dahi Puri, Egg Rolls, Mutton Burgers,
        Momos, Poha, Kachori, Paan and Gond Ke Laddu</string>

    <string name="eatery3_title">Hotel Shreemaya</string>
    <string name="eatery3_description">A classic experience of fine taste, quality food and over
        three decades of committed hospitality. Discover comfort &amp; convenience with intimate
        and warm hospitality, professional services, fine quality food and true value
        for money.</string>
    <string name="eatery3_location">R N T Marg</string>
    <string name="eatery3_maps">https://goo.gl/maps/mjsEMmkBMKt</string>
    <string name="eatery3_website">http://www.shreemaya.com/</string>

    <string name="eatery4_title">Shreemaya Celebration</string>
    <string name="eatery4_description">The Bakery &amp; Coffee Shop was established in 2007. Nestled in
        the mid of greenery, its refreshingly energizing atmosphere is our pride &amp; asset. Relish a
        wide variety of Breads, Cookies, Cakes, Chocolates, Pastries, Mocktails, Quick Snacks &amp;
        more..in a truly open &amp; peaceful location with spectacle of greenery.Kids areas is an
        add on lucration. Various play equipments like the climbing nets, slides,
        see-saw etc...have been placed, keeping our little guests engaged.</string>
    <string name="eatery4_location">Rajendra Nagar</string>
    <string name="eatery4_maps">https://goo.gl/maps/5Wtc2U2YvwH2</string>
    <string name="eatery4_timings">11:00 AM to 10:15 PM</string>
    <string name="eatery4_website">http://www.shreemaya.com</string>

    <string name="eatery5_title">Go Bananas - Sayaji Hotel</string>
    <string name="eatery5_description">When you want to enjoy time with friends and family while
        playing some indoor sports, Go Bananas at hotel Sayaji is the place to be at !! Get
        competitive in a bowling game at Indore\'s first Bowling Alley, which is also India\'s
        very first fully-automated Bowling Alley !! Or challenge friends over pocketing balls
        on a pool-table !! You may also bet your luck at the virtual games here !!
        And get kids to dash cars - bumper cars !!
        Do all this while enjoying good, peppy music and snacks, meals,
        alcoholic and non-alcoholic beverages, bakery products, and desserts here,
        all by hotel Sayaji !!</string>
    <string name="eatery5_location">Vijay Nagar</string>
    <string name="eatery5_maps">https://goo.gl/maps/j6tGU3itCCG2</string>
    <string name="eatery5_timings">11 AM to 12 AM</string>
    <string name="eatery5_website">sayajihotels.com</string>

    <string name="eatery6_title">Mug and Beans</string>
    <string name="eatery6_description">A highly-rated joint to enjoy a quick break with your
        colleagues. It serves a wide array of items from Fast Food, Italian cuisines and is
        quite well-known for its unique selection of dishes.</string>
    <string name="eatery6_location">Rajendra Nagar</string>
    <string name="eatery6_maps">https://goo.gl/maps/5hqk15ZmZRJ2</string>
    <string name="eatery6_timings">10 AM to 11 PM</string>

    <string name="eatery7_title">Indian Coffee House</string>
    <string name="eatery7_description">The Indian Coffee House has a long history !!
        In the pre-independence era, Government of India set up the Coffee Board, under the
        British rule, to promote drinking of coffee and sale of coffee seeds by farmers !!
        Post independence, the workers formed the co-operative societies in different states of
        India and renamed the network as INDIAN COFFEE HOUSE !! The first Indian Coffee House was
        opened in New Delhi on October 27, 1957 !! This is a very popular Indian style café serving
        South-Indian cuisine, snacks, meals, South Indian coffee, and much more, while being
        very friendly to the pocket !! Indian and Chinese main course dishes, rice dishes, and even
        salads can be ordered here either in full portions or half portions (remember the
        student budgets?) !! This is a great option when you are alone or when the two of you
        don't want to order the same dish, and taste various delicacies !! They have a mini
        thaali too !!</string>
    <string name="eatery7_location">Bhanwar kuwa, DAVV Takshila Parisar</string>
    <string name="eatery7_maps">https://goo.gl/maps/7p9sEpXggq82</string>
    <string name="eatery7_timings">10 AM to 9 PM</string>


    <!--String resources for shopping spots-->

    <string name="shopping1_title">MT Cloth Market</string>
    <string name="shopping1_description">If you want to buy the speciality of the beautiful city of
        Indore, handloom, then  MT Cloth Market is going to be a place for you. Treat yourself
        with buying clothing in wholesale at reasonable prices. Bargaining here will play an
        important role if you are actually buying the cloth in large quantities. If you are not
        really aware of the different kinds of cloth then don\'t worry because the shopkeepers
        here are like your ultimate guide for the same. They will guide you, advice you and will
        make sure that you at least leave their shop with four to five shopping bags.</string>
    <string name="shopping1_location">Maharaja Tukoji Rao Holker Cloth Market</string>
    <string name="shopping1_maps">https://goo.gl/maps/qkAJNjmxiVG2</string>
    <string name="shopping1_timings">10:00 AM to 08:30 PM</string>

    <string name="shopping2_title">Sitlamata Bazar</string>
    <string name="shopping2_description">One of the most famous bazaars in the city, Sitlamata
        Bazar is famous for its several stores selling retail clothing and sarees. The place is
        bustling with people all the time and you might find it hard to shop at times in this
        market. You will get the best sarees, be it Chanderi or Maheshwari, in the city to every
        woman’s pleasure. If you are soon to be bride, then this place is also amazing. Order for a
        lehenga chunri which will be made with the most awesome zaris and embroidery work. </string>
    <string name="shopping2_location">Maharaja Tukoji Rao Holker Cloth Market</string>
    <string name="shopping2_maps">https://goo.gl/maps/KA52T9omoTp</string>
    <string name="shopping2_timings">10:00 AM to 8:00 PM</string>

    <string name="shopping3_title">Treasure Island</string>
    <string name="shopping3_description">The highlights of Treasure Island are MAX, PVR,
        McDonald\'s, and Pizza Hut. MAX Retail, a division of Lifestyle International is the most
        famous fashion retail destination in the city. The USP of the store is its wide range of
        fashionable offering at a cost which suits everyone\'s pocket, specially youth. This store
        is also famous for being the 1st retail store in India by the renowned Landmark group.
        Treasure Island is comparable to the malls found in Noida and Gurgaon. Equipped with state
        of the art escalators and housed by showrooms of all leading brands, it\'s the bes
        t hangout in Indore (and most probably in the whole MP). It also has two Baristas
        (coffee shop) and a Rajdhani (a thali (buffet) restaurant).</string>
    <string name="shopping3_location">South Tukoganj, MG Road</string>
    <string name="shopping3_maps">https://goo.gl/maps/hZf795Bgspy</string>
    <string name="shopping3_timings">09:00 AM to 10:00 PM</string>

    <string name="shopping4_title">Mrignayani Showroom</string>
    <string name="shopping4_description">Located behind Gujarati Girl\'s college, Mrignayani
        Showroom is the MP government\'s exclusive handicraft store which serves you with a wide
        variety of artefacts that the city\’s creativity has in store. Do not forget to buy hand
        crafted leather toys and other handicraft items such as bangles, show pieces and other
        decorative pieces. Haggling over prices is not going to save you from spending here as it
        is a government run showroom. But don\'t worry, you are not going to repent spending even
        a penny out here. </string>
    <string name="shopping4_location">Mahatma Gandhi Road</string>
    <string name="shopping4_maps">https://goo.gl/maps/qGGZ73MPjBA2</string>
    <string name="shopping4_timings">11:00 AM to 8:30 PM</string>
    <string name="shopping4_website">http://wwww.mrignayani.com</string>

    <string name="shopping5_title">C21 Mall</string>
    <string name="shopping5_description">Another Good Mall on AB Road having exclusive shops of
        many international brands like Tommy Hilfiger, Madame,Wills, Arrow, Calvin Klein, United
        Colors of Benneton, Fastrack, Adidas, Nike, Levis, Monte Carlo, French Connection (FCUK)
        and indian brands like Biba, Ritu wears' Biglife etc It also accomodates Satyam Cineplex,
        CCD, and a 4D theatre named Storm.</string>
    <string name="shopping5_location">Scheme No.54, Vijay Nagar </string>
    <string name="shopping5_timings">10:00 AM to 9:30 PM</string>
    <string name="shopping5_website">http://www.c21malls.co.in</string>
    <string name="shopping5_maps">https://goo.gl/maps/FifpNniR6Vs</string>

    <string name="shopping6_title">Shoppers Stop</string>
    <string name="shopping6_description">A famous elite shopping store in India which sells a blend
        of a lot of famous brands. An expensive store but very reliable in the sense of quality.
        Cheaper for the tourists and non-residents since its got a better prices than overseas. </string>
    <string name="shopping6_location">LIG gurudwara, A.B. Road</string>
    <string name="shopping6_maps">https://goo.gl/maps/VVKF9w3dT4x</string>
    <string name="shopping6_timings">11 AM to 9 PM</string>
    <string name="shopping6_website">http://www.shoppersstop.com</string>

</resources>
